ploose.com 2018-05-04

# Privacy – Injury Survey

PRIVACY POLICY

Last Updated: May 3, 2016

Welcome to www.InjurySurvey.com, the Web site (“Site”) of InjurySurvey.com (“InjurySurvey.com”, “we” or “us”).

InjurySurvey.com respects the privacy of those who access and/or use the Site (“you”, “your”, “user” or collectively “users”) and is committed to protecting the personally identifiable information we collect.

1\. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY  
If the online Privacy Policy changes, we will post all changes in an amended version with a new “Last Updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy.

2\. INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT  
We collect two types of information from you. The first type is personal information that you actively choose to disclose (“Active Information”) and the second type is anonymous aggregate information collected in a manner not visible to you or others visiting the Site (“Passive Information”).

a. Active Information. Examples of personally identifiable data that you provide to us may include your name, address, email address and telephone number. In providing Active Information, you consent and agree to being contacted with information related to your inquiry and/or information regarding our or third parties’ products and services. If you provide personally identifiable data to us, you may later elect to have that information deleted from our files, or kept from being used for purposes other than for the service requested, by following the opt-out procedures set forth below.

b. Passive Information. We record information relating to your use of the Site, such as the information you click on, your browser type, IP address, referring URL, and timestamp information. We use this type of information to administer the Site and provide the highest possible level of service to you. We may also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Site.

3\. HOW COLLECTED INFORMATION IS USED  
We will share or sell your Active and/or Passive Information with our marketing partners and affiliates to provide you legal services and commercial products that may be of interest. We also use this information to better target content in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience. Please note that we also reserve the right to, and will, rent, sell, share or transfer your personal information to third parties for any legally permissible purpose in our sole discretion.

4\. USE OF COOKIES  
We use cookies to store users’ preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that users are not repeatedly offered the same material and to customize any newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We may share, sell, or license cookies collected from your browser and hard drive to third-party advertisers. These authorized third parties may link your name, address, and e-mail address to other information which they collect, such as past online/offline purchase information and Web usage from other sites. These authorized companies are contractually bound to secure the data they receive. You may disable cookies by adjusting the settings on your Web browser. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. Each browser is different, so you may wish to review the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. Note, however, that you may be required to enable cookies in order to use certain functions on our Site.

5\. INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE  
We may share, license, or sell information we collect to third parties for various marketing purposes, including their online marketing programs. We also reserve the unequivocal right to release all your information, to the maximum extent permitted by law in the event that (i) we believe that the Site is being or has been used to commit unlawful acts, (ii) the information is subpoenaed or otherwise required in a court proceeding, (iii) you violate or breach an agreement with the Site, (iv) you have submitted fraudulent or otherwise invalid information to this Site, (v) we believe that you may harm, or have harmed, the property or other rights of us, our members, our employees, the Site’s other users or any other third party, (vi) we are sold to or otherwise acquired by any individual, entity or organization (i.e. to a successor entity in the event of sale of the business, including merger, bankruptcy or other ownership change), or (vii) when we otherwise deem it necessary or appropriate. We may disclose any record or communication to any third party when we, in our sole discretion, determine the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the requirements of the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time, or any other applicable state or federal law, rule or regulation.

6\. OPTING-OUT  
You may opt-out of having some of your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes when providing us with this information. You may also decline to provide certain personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly or at all as a result.

If you no longer wish to receive newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by contacting us as provided in this Privacy Policy. You may continue to receive email communications from us for up to ten (10) business days from the time we receive your Unsubscribe – [Unsubscribe](http://unsubscribe.injurysurvey.com/) request. Please note that InjurySurvey.com can only control its own mailing list and policies. Third party advertisers that maintain their own mailing lists may send communications that advertise our services, and you may need to contact these parties directly in order to stop receiving their communications.

7\. ACCESS/ACCURACY  
To the extent that you do provide us with certain personally identifiable information, we strive to maintain the accuracy of this information. Our goal is to provide a means to contact us should you need to update or correct your information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible through the Site, you may send updates and corrections about your personally identifiable information to support@digitizeiq.com and we will make reasonable efforts to make changes to the information we hold as soon as possible.

8\. SECURITY OF INFORMATION  
Use of the Site is at your own risk. Nonetheless, we do make reasonable efforts to secure your information. Such efforts may include but are not limited to monitoring of our network and data for intrusions. We also use industry-accepted standards to protect your information, including SSL encryption if and when transmitting any sensitive information. We have implemented certain physical, encrypted, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. Communications you may have with us via email or mail may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your sending information.

9\. LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES  
The Site may contain links to third party Web sites including sites with which we have no affiliation. We are not responsible for their privacy practices. It is recommended you read the privacy policies on all such third party Web sites.

10\. CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS  
Beginning January 1, 2005, under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to either (i) a list detailing the categories of information shared and the entities to which such information was provided; or (ii) to be notified of a mechanism by which a consumer may opt-out of having their information shared with third parties. We have elected the second option. To opt-out of having your information shared with third parties, simply email us support@digitizeiq.com with the words “Opt Out” in the subject header.

11\. CHILDREN  
If you are under 18, you may not access or use the Site. BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE, YOU REPRESENT THAT YOU ARE AT LEAST 18. In compliance with COPPA, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from users under 13.

12\. NON-U.S. USERS  
FOR USERS VISITING THE SITE FROM THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA OR OTHER NON-U.S. TERRITORIES, PLEASE NOTE THAT ANY DATA YOU VOLUNTARILY PROVIDED US WILL BE TRANSFERRED OUTSIDE THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA OR SUCH OTHER NON-U.S. TERRITORY FOR USE BY InjurySurvey.com FOR ANY OF THE PURPOSES DESCRIBED HEREIN.

13\. CONTACT INFORMATION  
For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, or you wish to opt-out as provided above in this policy, you may email us at support@digitizeiq.com or you can send correspondence to the following address:

DigitizeIQ LLC  
10624 S. Eastern Ave,  
Ste A-910  
Henderson, NV 89052  
support@digitizeiq.com
